(Sheldon:)Why are you up?
(Leonard:)How am I supposed to sleep?
(Leonard:)I've been married
less than 24 hours,
(Leonard:)and my wife
isn't speaking to me.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps you can think of this
in a more positive light.
(Sheldon:)In one day,
you've managed to do
(Sheldon:)what it takes many couples
decades to achieve.
(knocking on door)
(Sheldon:)Hi.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)You couldn't sleep either?
(Leonard:)Of course not.
(Sheldon:)Me neither.
(Sheldon:)But I just had
a tickle in my throat.
(Sheldon:)Not profound marital problems.
(Leonard:)What are we gonna do?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)Please, tell me
how I can fix it.
(Sheldon:)Glad you asked.
(Sheldon:)As I see it, there's
a simple solution.
(Sheldon:)Your lips had a dalliance
with the lips of another woman.
(Sheldon:)It seems only
logical that
(Sheldon:)to restore balance
to the relationship,
(Sheldon:)you should find another man
and dally with him.
(Sheldon:)And by dally,
I mean some hardcore